35 Wright Ave, Truro, N.S. (902) 893-1301 andrewgates@hotmail.com

Andrew Gates

Skills:

Programming: Experience using: PHP, Java, ASP .Net, JavaScript, JQuery, Angular2, Android, MySQL, HTML5, Visual Basic, AJAX, JSON, JIRA, Node JS

Other IT Skills: A basic knowledge and understanding of Networking

Team oriented thinking: Well versed experience in team based environments, critical team thinking, as well as team based projects honed through 16 years from working in a military environment.

Great in a leadership role: Have experience in leading teams to a specific goal and meeting that goal efficiently and effectively while maintaining team focus. Strong leadership skills developed through twelve years of working in a high stress environment

Innovative: Experience in taking minimal information and producing the required results.

Adaptive to ever-changing situations: Experienced in an ever-changing environment where unexpected incidents occur frequently and able to adapt quickly.

Work Experience

Pay 4 Performance Marketing **PHP Developer**

2017 - 2018

Designed and Coded an Email Parser to search through emails in a mailbox to

pick out any relevant information to the company and enter it into the database. Redesigned and Coded changes to the Company's Employee site. Worked on an app to send a fax using the Company's dialing provider.

Department of National Defense - Casual

2000 - present

Infantry Reserves

Responsible for training of fellow soldiers

Works in a fast paced environment which has the ability to change constantly Help foster self-confidence in other soldiers through evaluation Maintained the high standards set by the CAF and DND

Premiere Van Lines

2014 - 2015

Driver Helper

Responsible for packing Clients items Responsible for loading the truck Unload the truck Unpack Clients items

Securitas Canada 2012 - 2014

Security Guard

Responsible for Technicians Safety

Responsible for areas that are under guard

Detect and prevent thefts and vandalism

Enforce regulations of establishment and maintain order

Ensure safety and emergency procedures are followed

Bartlett's Plastic and Precision Machining

2007 - 2011

Warehouse Department Manager

Responsible for organizing incoming and outgoing shipments.

Created Customs documents for international shipments

Trained team members on the use of warehouse machinery

Worked in a fast paced high stress environment

Responsible for order accuracy

Education and Training

Graduated IT Course Web Dev at NSCC Truro

CPR and First Aid Certificates, St. John's Ambulance

WHMIS Training

Current

Current

References

Available Upon Request